{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952662019","data":{"timestamp":" 946952662018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 6adc5f88-de02-4d88-bbfb-fb0b918124ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_niko_nawe-niko-pana"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952682328","data":{"timestamp":" 946952682327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" dd90fa85-3bf2-4b00-abef-74e5eed30ece"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_wawe-hula-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952682730","data":{"timestamp":" 946952682730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" dd90fa85-3bf2-4b00-abef-74e5eed30ece"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_wawe-hula-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952695061","data":{"timestamp":" 946952695060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" dd90fa85-3bf2-4b00-abef-74e5eed30ece"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_wawe-hula-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952724596","data":{"timestamp":" 946952724596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 9c7a678f-9dcf-44cd-adb6-66bd8ca77086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_biga-ziwa-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952735540","data":{"timestamp":" 946952735540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 9c7a678f-9dcf-44cd-adb6-66bd8ca77086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_biga-ziwa-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952778359","data":{"timestamp":" 946952778359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 9c7a678f-9dcf-44cd-adb6-66bd8ca77086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_koko_bibi-koko-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" koko"," userResponse":" koko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952814009","data":{"timestamp":" 946952814009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 08f79b84-9f9e-434e-9273-3b132c9dcdbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_wawe-hula-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952849886","data":{"timestamp":" 946952849886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 08f79b84-9f9e-434e-9273-3b132c9dcdbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_wako-nipe-gani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952862727","data":{"timestamp":" 946952862727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 08f79b84-9f9e-434e-9273-3b132c9dcdbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_koko_koko-wenu-kima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" koko"," userResponse":" koko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952864293","data":{"timestamp":" 946952864293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 08f79b84-9f9e-434e-9273-3b132c9dcdbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_koko_koko-wenu-kima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952892827","data":{"timestamp":" 946952892826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 00e16c77-2d7c-432b-bcf1-4f08caee1efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_biga-ziwa-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wako"," userResponse":" wako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952893801","data":{"timestamp":" 946952893801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 00e16c77-2d7c-432b-bcf1-4f08caee1efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_biga-ziwa-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952900331","data":{"timestamp":" 946952900330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 00e16c77-2d7c-432b-bcf1-4f08caee1efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_biga-ziwa-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952908897","data":{"timestamp":" 946952908897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 00e16c77-2d7c-432b-bcf1-4f08caee1efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ko.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wako_biga-ziwa-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952940980","data":{"timestamp":" 946952940980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952941774","data":{"timestamp":" 946952941774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952949686","data":{"timestamp":" 946952949686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952950566","data":{"timestamp":" 946952950566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952957269","data":{"timestamp":" 946952957269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952958371","data":{"timestamp":" 946952958370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952965933","data":{"timestamp":" 946952965933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ko.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952968980","data":{"timestamp":" 946952968980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952974614","data":{"timestamp":" 946952974613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.le.rand.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952980314","data":{"timestamp":" 946952980313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" f3dee540-f321-4bb2-9a01-3966437453e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ko.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952989581","data":{"timestamp":" 946952989580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952989804","data":{"timestamp":" 946952989804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952990769","data":{"timestamp":" 946952990769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952992044","data":{"timestamp":" 946952992044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952994947","data":{"timestamp":" 946952994947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952995793","data":{"timestamp":" 946952995792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952996108","data":{"timestamp":" 946952996107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946952997340","data":{"timestamp":" 946952997340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953000829","data":{"timestamp":" 946953000829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953001813","data":{"timestamp":" 946953001813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953002067","data":{"timestamp":" 946953002067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953003010","data":{"timestamp":" 946953003010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953005854","data":{"timestamp":" 946953005853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953006886","data":{"timestamp":" 946953006886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953007360","data":{"timestamp":" 946953007360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953011903","data":{"timestamp":" 946953011903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953012005","data":{"timestamp":" 946953012004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 48c7ffe5-69a6-49c4-b48b-f87961b832d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953024526","data":{"timestamp":" 946953024526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953024749","data":{"timestamp":" 946953024748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953025713","data":{"timestamp":" 946953025713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953026988","data":{"timestamp":" 946953026988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953029873","data":{"timestamp":" 946953029873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953030717","data":{"timestamp":" 946953030717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953031033","data":{"timestamp":" 946953031033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953032271","data":{"timestamp":" 946953032271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953035776","data":{"timestamp":" 946953035776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953036760","data":{"timestamp":" 946953036760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953037015","data":{"timestamp":" 946953037015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953037959","data":{"timestamp":" 946953037958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953040801","data":{"timestamp":" 946953040801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953041839","data":{"timestamp":" 946953041839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953042315","data":{"timestamp":" 946953042315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953046858","data":{"timestamp":" 946953046858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953047051","data":{"timestamp":" 946953047051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" 8f3d9da9-3def-4317-ab1f-9ee741813c08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953059549","data":{"timestamp":" 946953059549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953059775","data":{"timestamp":" 946953059775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953060742","data":{"timestamp":" 946953060742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953062021","data":{"timestamp":" 946953062021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953064941","data":{"timestamp":" 946953064941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953065789","data":{"timestamp":" 946953065788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953066105","data":{"timestamp":" 946953066105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953067339","data":{"timestamp":" 946953067339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953070846","data":{"timestamp":" 946953070846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953071834","data":{"timestamp":" 946953071834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953072091","data":{"timestamp":" 946953072091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953073037","data":{"timestamp":" 946953073037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953075916","data":{"timestamp":" 946953075916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953076953","data":{"timestamp":" 946953076953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953077431","data":{"timestamp":" 946953077431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953081953","data":{"timestamp":" 946953081953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953082105","data":{"timestamp":" 946953082105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.le.show.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953088458","data":{"timestamp":" 946953088458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_052410"," gameId":" cbee66b8-3d14-484e-8352-4d8c6b83b8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}